<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WWU Cybersecurity Club</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WWU Cybersecurity Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2021 WWU Cybersecurity Club</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 19:38:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberForce 2021 Competition Starts Soon</title>
      <link>/posts/cyberforce2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 19:38:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cyberforce2021/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity Club is interested in students to join us for the CyberForce competition! The Department of Energy hosts an annual competition called &amp;ldquo;CyberForce&amp;rdquo;. This competition focuses on defense and securing networks from attacks as opposed to traditional competitions focused on attack. Last year students were tasked with defending a wind farm and this year we are defending a hydroelectric dam. These scenarios are modeled after real world infrastructure and give students extremely valuable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WWU Cybersecurity Certificate</title>
      <link>/posts/certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 22:31:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/certificate/</guid>
      <description> New WWU Cybersecurity Certificate Available! Hey everyone! WWU has created a 16 credit Cybersecurity certificate! Its offered on the Bellingham and Poulsbo campuses, and is open to most students (Sadly, Computer Science department majors are not eligible). For more info check out the link here.
We encourage everyone interested to check it out! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Club Update</title>
      <link>/posts/club-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 20:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/club-update/</guid>
      <description>The Cyber Security club is back! It&amp;rsquo;s currently being rebuilt by Noah (Co-President), Sid (Co-President), Nathan, and Douglas. We aim to have everything up and running before the first week of class (September 22nd). Check back here soon for more information on the club, events, and other happenings. Our main method of communication has been discord, the link for which can also be found at the contact and about pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 20:03:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Info  cscwwu@gmail.com Message any Officer on Discord  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 19:48:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/leadership/</guid>
      <description> This page will contain the position and name of current officers. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calendar/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Blogs &amp;amp; News  Krebs on Security Cisco Talos Kayne McGladrey Arstechnica Daniel Miessler Phoronix Ycombinator HackerNews
  Programming and Computer Science: Tutorials and Resources Programming  Codecademy Learn You a Haskell  Computer Science and Operating Systems  Operating Systems: Three Easy Pieces Computer Networks: A Systems Approach Linux Academy (requires a (free) account)  Resource Dumps  What Every CS Student Should Know Open Source Computer Science Degree Curated Programming Resources OWASP Security Cheatsheet  Security  Portswigger Academy (Webapp Pentesting)  Cloud  AWS Training  Tools &amp;amp; Other  Markdown Tutorial Github Git Handbook The Git Book (overkill for beginners) Vimtutor: If you&amp;rsquo;ve installed vim, simply run vimtutor in your shell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Western Washington University Cybersecurity Club</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Cybersecurity Club! We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to having a great year in 2021 &amp;amp; 2021. Check out the calendar page for our future activities.
Our plans for this year include:
* Capture-the-Flag competitions and CCDC practice
* CCNA and networking study sessions
* Creating virtual testing environments on top of physical hardware
* Trips to visit security companies &amp;amp; teams
* Internship and job-seeking guidance, resume reviews, etc</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>